

IVÁN ORLANDO ANAYA CARREOLA

OBJETIVO

I develop and apply the knowledge acquired during my academic training and work experience, work in a team, always focused on achieving and meeting the established objectives, contributing professional and personal ideas. I make active decisions and commit to demonstrating continuous improvement.

INTERESES

- Digital education
- Technology
- Personal self-improvement
- Music
- Literature
- Cinema
- Writing music
- Nature

INFORMACIÓN DE CONTACTO



(55)20877922



(55)16753916



orlandocarreola@gmail.com



Sta. Cecilia 123

Col. Hogar y Redención Del. Álvaro Obregón

IDIOMAS

English C1

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, CENTER FOR TECHNOLOGICAL AND SERVICE STUDIES.

Obtained certification in Food Analysis and Preservation Methods. 2012.

UNIVERSITY OF MUSIC AND AUDIO G MARTELL

Bachelor of Arts: Musician and Composer, specialized in Electric Bass. 2017.

UNIVERSIDAD TÉCNOCLOGÍCA DE MÉXICO (UNITEC)

Software and Network Engineering | Currently studying.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Conekta

Technical Support for Websites June 2023- June 2024

- Expert in integrating Conekta API to optimize the functionality of websites developed with API or CMS.
- Troubleshooting technical issues and ensuring a smooth user experience during online transactions.
- Maintaining integrations and technical documentation.

San Ángel Digital

Production and Development

February 2023 - June 2023

- Development and maintenance of websites, focusing on optimizing user experience and performance.
- Management of WHM/CPanel servers to ensure their operation and data security.
- Troubleshooting technical issues and improving hardware efficiency in computer systems.

Marriott

Bilingual Customer Service Representative October 2022 - January 2023

 Support in handling reservations and addressing customer inquiries.

OXED (Oxford Education)

IT Apprentice

January 2022 - June 2022

- Assistance in the IT department.
- Handling databases, detecting, and correcting errors in digital platforms.

COURSES

- Microsoft Office 365
- Microsoft Teams: Creation of comunucation and colaboration scenarios.
- Python sin fronteras: HTML, CSS, Flask and MySQL.
- Java Script Moderno, Guía Definitiva.
- Desarrollo Web Completo con HTML, CSS3, JS AJAX PHP y MySQL
- Excel total.